https://alfabank.com/privacy-and-cookies/

Home
Privacy and Cookies
Alfa-Bank respects your personal privacy. We value the confidentiality of the information which you provide when you visit our website(s) or other online facilities and register as a “user”. Alfa-Bank is committed to complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws.
By using our website, you signify your agreement to the terms of use and consent to the collection and use of your information to analyse web traffic. If you do not agree with any term in this policy, please stop using our website(s) immediately.
Collection of personal information
We will not collect any information about individuals, except where it is specifically and knowingly provided by them. Examples of such information are:
name
telephone number
company name
email address
The information collected will be used to provide you with the information requested by you.
You may opt out of these services at any time if you wish.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of text which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree (or your browser agrees automatically if you have set it up in that way), your browser adds that text in a small file.
We have included a full list of the cookies used on alfabank.com below (cookies used by this site), along with a definition of what the cookie is used for.
Consent to use of cookies
Cookies collect information about how visitors use the site, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies do not collect information which identifies a visitor and Alfa Banking Group will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. All information is aggregated and therefore anonymous. By using the website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.
How to control and delete cookies
Alfa Banking Group treats all the data held with the utmost care and security. However, if you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by alfabank.com, or indeed any other website, or if you wish to receive notification of cookie placement requests or decline cookies completely, you can do this through your browser settings. The Help function within your browser should tell you how. Please be aware that declining or denying cookies may prevent you from being able to use the website to its highest capability.
Alternatively, you may wish to visit www.aboutcookies.org which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of browsers as well as more general information about cookies.
Cookies used by this website
This is a list of the main cookies set by the alfabank.com website, and what each is used for:
Analytics
Name
Explanation
Aether
We use Gaia Insight to enable us to understand how visitors interact with this site particularly the paths visitors take through the site. This data is used to help understand how visitors interact with the site and the way in which they navigate through it. Your IP address and other personally identifiable data is not associated with any other data held by Gaia Insight.
_ga, _gat
This site uses Google Analytics,  a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics sets a cookie  in order to evaluate our use of our website and compile reports on user  activity.
Google stores the information  collected by the cookie on servers in the United States. Google may also  transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or  where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google  will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. By using  this site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the  manner and for the purposes set out above.
_ceg.s, _ceg.u
We use Crazy Egg to see how  visitors interact with areas of a page. No personally identifiable data is  captured during this process.
Visitor preference, rendering browser specific features
Table of cookies used on this site for Visitor preference, rendering browser specific features
Name
Explanation
Duration
seen_cookie_message
We use this cookie to determine when the cookie disclaimer message has been closed in order that it is not then shown on subsequent visits.
1 year
Use of information and data protection
Alfa Banking Group is committed to the online privacy of all its users. The Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC (“the Directive”), which has been implemented by most countries in the European Union, safeguards the privacy of an individual’s personal details. Alfa Banking Group has adopted its principles as the basis for its worldwide data protection policy. We collect, record and use your personal information (name, company name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number) only with your consent and authorisation. Typically, this will be when you make enquiries or register for information or services.
We may share non-personal aggregate statistics (group) data about our site visitors’ traffic patterns with partners or other parties. However, we do not sell or share any information about individual users.
Your rights
In addition to the company’s safeguards, your personal data is protected in the UK by the Data Protection Act. This provides amongst other things that the data we hold about you should be processed lawfully and fairly. It should be accurate, relevant and not excessive. The information should be kept up to date, where necessary, and not retained for longer than is necessary. It should be kept securely to prevent unauthorised access by other people. You have the right to see what is held about you and correct any inaccuracies.
Transfer of data
Personal data will only be transferred between Alfa Banking Group locations and third-party locations if adequate protection (being that which meets the requirements of the Directive) of personal data can be reasonably assumed at the locations concerned. Where we are required to do so, we will implement appropriate contracts to ensure the privacy of your personal details.
Security
We will take reasonable precautions to protect personal information in our possession from loss, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. You should be aware, however, that communications over the Internet (which includes e-mails to Alfa Banking Group and registering as a user on our website(s)) are not secure unless they have been encrypted and we do not accept any responsibility for any errors or omissions which arise from circumstances outside of our reasonable control.
Our website may contain links to other websites that are operated by third parties. Other websites may also reference or link to our website. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites.
Policy changes
Alfa Banking Group reserves the right to amend or modify this policy at any time, whether or not in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy laws.
Enquiries
Any questions or concerns which you may have about this policy should be emailed to us. We will investigate and attempt to resolve any concerns or complaints regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with this policy.
Corporate Profile
About Us
Our Strategy
Governance
Internal Control and Audit
Our Business
Investment Banking
Corporate Banking Services
Search for:
